Guide to the John Henry and Anna Botsford Comstock papers, 1833-1955,
Comstock, John Henry and Anna Botsford papers,
- Correspondence
  - John Henry Comstock professional correspondence
    - A-F
      - Best, Lyman Austin, 1889-09-28 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Best, Lyman Austin, 1890-02-16 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Best, Lyman Austin, 1891-05-09 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Best, Lyman Austin, 1892-06-20 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Best, Lyman Austin, 1892-09-03 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Best, Lyman Austin, 1893-08-10 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Best, Lyman Austin, 1896-12-17 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Bethel, E., 1891-06-30 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Bethel, E., 1891-07-08 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Bethune, Charles James Stewart, 1887-11-25 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Beutenmuller, William, 1890-01-21 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Beutenmuller, William, 1890-02-04 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Beutenmuller, William, 1890-03-25 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Beutenmuller, William, 1890-08-07 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Beutenmuller, William, 1891-06-15 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Beutenmuller, William, 1891-08-08 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Beutenmuller, William, 1891-08-21 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Beutenmuller, William, 1891-08-27 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Beutenmuller, William, 1891-10-18 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Beutenmuller, William, 1892-07-01 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Beutenmuller, William, 1900-01-04 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Beutenmuller, William, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Bidwell, Peter Swartout, 1899-03-01 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Bidwell, Peter Swartout, 1899-12-20 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Bird, Alice E., 1892-03-02 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Bird, Alice E., 1892-04-14 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Bird, Alice E., 1892-11-10 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Blanchard, Nathan Weston, 1892-02-26 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Bland, H.M., 1892-02-17 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Blatchford, N.F., 1886-10-16 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Blatchford, N.F., 1891-05-30 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Blatchford, N.F., 1891-06-30 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Blatchford, N.F., Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Bliss, Clara A., 1894-01-11 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Bliss, Clara A., 1894-07-26 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Boalt, Eben, 1892-02-27 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Boardman, Douglass, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Bolivar/Bolinas, Sgn., 1899-06-01 (Box 6, Folder 20)
        Professor of Entomology, University of Madrid
      - Bolles, George Albert, 1891-09-05 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Bonnell, H.S., 1889-01-22 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Bonner's Sons, Robert, 1889-01-14 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Bonner's Sons, Robert, 1889-11-23 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Bonner's Sons, Robert, 1889-11-25 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1886-01-01 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1886-01-04 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1886-02-13 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1886-07-14 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1887-04-06 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1887-10-14 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1887-12-20 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1888-06-20 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1888-11-17 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1889-12-11 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1890-05-14 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1890-10-14 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1891-01-13 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1891-02-12 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1891-05-05 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1891-11-12 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1891-12-09 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1892-09-30 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1893-02-14 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1893-04-17 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1893-06-12 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1893-12-13 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Bool, H. and Co., 1894-10-15 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Borst, May M., 1893-08-16 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Bosch, Charles F., 1886-08-09 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Bowker, Richard Rogers, 1890-01-31 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Bowker, Richard Rogers, 1890-05 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Bowker, Richard Rogers, 1890-09-02 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Bradford, George D., 1891-04-13 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Brainard, G.G. Austin, 1890-10-04 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Brainard, G.G. Austin, 1892-05-22 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Brainard, Henry A., 1891-01-25 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Brainard, Henry A., 1891-12-30 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Brainard, Henry A., 1892-01-30 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Brainerd, William L., 1891-07-01 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Bramson, V., 1892-02-11 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Brandage, Katherine, 1891-09-21 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Brandage, Katherine, 1892-09-15 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1885-08-17 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1885-09-03 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1885-10-25 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1885-11-09 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1885-11-21 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1886-01-23 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1886-02-04 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1886-03-14 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1886-05-06 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1886-07-06 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1886-10-27 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1887-01-30 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1887-02-10 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1887-02-21 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1887-03-27 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1887-05-30 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1887-07-17 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1888-04-13 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1888-05-02 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1890-04-13 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1890-05-22 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1891-03-13 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1891-12-01 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1892-01-22 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1892-10-31 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1893-08-22 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Branner, John Casper, 1896-04-21 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Branner, John Casper, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Breckinridge, M.C., 1889-11-14 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Breckinridge, M.C., 1890-11-18 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Breckinridge, Roeliff Morton, 1891-09-26 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Breckinridge, Roeliff Morton, 1891-10-06 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Breckinridge, Roeliff Morton, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Breternitz, R., 1889-03-08 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Brewer, Orville, 1888-05-17 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Brewer, Orville, 1891-04-10 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Brewer, Orville, 1892-02-01 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Brewer, Orville, 1894-09-25 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Briggs, E.W., 1890-10-29 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Bristol, George Prentice, 1892-06-06 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Brockway, Zebulon Reed, 1885-06-03 (Box 2, Folder 5)
        New York State Reformatory
        Elmira, New York
      - Brockway, Zebulon Reed, 1885-06-10 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Brooks, Arthur B., 1892-01-01 (Box 5, Folder 4)
        Chemical Dealer
        Ithaca, New York
      - Brotherhood Wine Co., 1892-06-11 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Brotherhood Wine Co., 1893-05-03 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Broun, William LeRoy, 1888-03-09 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Brown, C.A., 1892-04-01 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Brown, Charles Carroll, 1893-06-23 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Brown, Charles Carroll, 1894-02-26 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Brown, Edmund Fowler, 1887-09-23 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Brown, Edmund Fowler, 1894-01-15 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Brown, J.E., 1888-01-14 (Box 2, Folder 27)
        Collector of State Tax
      - Brown, J.E., 1894-06-04 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Brown, Lyman Van Winkle, 1893-06-18 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Brown, Lyman Van Winkle, 1894-06-04 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Brown, S.C., 1889-10-25 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Brownell, J.B., 1889-05-29 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Brownell, J.B., 1889-08-19 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Brownell, J.B., 1890-06-19 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Bruce, David, 1890-02-25 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Bruce, David, 1890-04-01 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Bruce, David, 1890-05-05 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Bruce, David, 1890-05-13 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Bruce, David, 1891-03-26 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Bruce, David, 1891-06-29 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Bruce, David, 1891-07-11 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Bruce, David, 1891-08-20 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Bruce, David, 1891-09-07 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Bruce, David, 1891-09-28 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Bruce, David, 1891-10-24 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Bruce, David, 1891-11-03 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Bruce, David, 1891-11-08 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Bruce, David, 1891-11-15 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Bruce, David, 1892-05-01 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Bruce, David, 1892-05-16 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Bruce, David, 1892-05-18 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Bruce, David, 1892-06-11 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Bruce, David, 1892-12-01 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Bruce, David, 1892-12-06 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Bruce, David, 1893-08-16 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Bruce, David, 1893-08-31 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Bruce, David, 1893-10-12 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Bruce, David, 1894-01-17 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Bruce, David, 1894-02-28 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Bruce, David, 1894-05-02 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Bruce, William, 1888-09-06 (Box 3, Folder 2)
        Paterson? c/o Rev. Thomas Beecher, Elmira, New York
        Yonkers, New York
      - Bruner, Lawrence, 1889-01-09 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Bruner, Lawrence, 1889-06-10 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Bruner, Lawrence, 1892-10-19 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Bruner, Lawrence, 1892-10-28 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Bruner, Lawrence, 1892-12-01 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Bruner, Lawrence, 1893-02-11 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Bruner, Lawrence, 1893-04-20 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Bruner, Lawrence, 1893-06-14 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Bruner, Lawrence, 1893-07-07 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Bruner, Lawrence, 1894-01-26 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Bruner, Lawrence, 1894-02-12 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Brunk, Thomas Lafayette, 1885-12-15 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Brunk, Thomas Lafayette, 1887-04-04 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Brunk, Thomas Lafayette, 1887-09-02 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Brunk, Thomas Lafayette, 1887-12-16 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Brunk, Thomas Lafayette, 1888-01-28 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Brunk, Thomas Lafayette, 1888-02-16 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Brunn, Hermin E., 1886-01-12 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Brunn, Hermin E., 1890-10-10 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Brunn, Hermin E., 1891-01-26 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Buchellar, J. Edward, 1885-05-16 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Buckhart, William A., 1887-12-28 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Buckley, Katherine L., 1891-08-13 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Bunn, George B., 1890-01-18 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Burnett, Archie Collamore, 1886-06-24 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Burnham, W.A., 1893-12-11 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Burnham, W.A., 1893-12-14 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Burr, George Lincoln, 1889-03-10 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Burr, George Lincoln, 1889-08-16 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Burr, George Lincoln, 1892-05-09 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Burrage, Gertrude, 1893-01-03 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Bush and Dean, 1890-09-08 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Bush and Dean, 1892-12-20 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Bush and Dean, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Butler, James, 1901-05-07 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Cadle, C., Jr., 1885-09-18 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Cadle, C., Jr., 1887-06-15 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Caldwell, George Chapman, 1892-05-19 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Caldwell, George Chapman, 1892-05-21 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Caldwell, George Chapman, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Callaghan, W.A., 1892-02-23 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Calverly, William, 1886-04-10 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Calverly, William, 1889-03-05 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Calvert, E.T., 1892-03-23 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Calvert, H.J., 1891-12-29 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Calvert, Philip Powell, 1890-03-13 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Campbell, L.A. and Co., 1890-08-11 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Campbell, L.A. and Co., 1890-11-06 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Candell, A.N., 1890-12-10 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Canner, E.J., 1888-08-17 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Carbutt, John, 1890-09-17 (Box 4, Folder 3)
        Dry plate works
      - Carder, A.C., 1885-07-27 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Carlisle, Ellen E., 1886-03-17 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Carlisle, Ellen E., 1886-05-23 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Carman, Alice, 1892-04-28 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Carman, E.A., 1882-06-17 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Carmody, Thomas, 1893-11-14 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Carr, Jeanne C., 1892-01-22 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Carter, H.H., Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Carter, Mrs. W.C., 1894-04-05 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Carter, Truman Post, 1889-08-06 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Carter, Truman Post, 1890-10-02 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Carter, Truman Post, 1890-11-03 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Carter, Truman Post, 1891-01-03 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Carter, Truman Post, 1891-09-03 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Carter, Truman Post, 1891-10-31 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Carter, Truman Post, 1892-02-14 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Cary, Evelyn Rumsey, 1899-05-02 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Cassidy, Jessie Jane (Mrs. Sidney Arthur Saunders), 1891-02-20 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Cassino, Samuel Edson, 1888-04-18 (Box 2, Folder 29)
        Publisher
        Massachusetts
      - Cassino, Samuel Edson, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Cavanna, Prof. S., 1886-07-05 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Century, The, 1900-06-21 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Chamberlain, Jessie C., 1888-09-12 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Chamberlain, Joseph Redington, 1889-05-20 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Chamberlain, Joseph Redington, 1889-06-10 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Chaplin, A.J., 1889-11-16 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Chapman, C.E., 1889-05-28 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Chapman, C.E., 1889-06-01 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Charlton, John, 1892-03-16 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Chase, John Manly, 1890-08-15 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Chester, Frederick Dixon Walthall, 1888-05-10 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Chideman, Edward F., 1894-03-28 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Chilcott, Ellery Channing, 1890-02-02 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Chittenden, Frank Hurlbut, 1885-01-14 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Chittenden, Frank Hurlbut, 1886-02-01 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Chittenden, Frank Hurlbut, 1886-02-10 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Chittenden, Frank Hurlbut, 1886-03-04 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Chittenden, Frank Hurlbut, 1886-03-08 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Chittenden, Frank Hurlbut, 1887-03-28 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Chittenden, Frank Hurlbut, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Chope, E.B., 1889-05-21 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Chope, E.B., 1889-07-26 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Chope, E.B., 1889-08-31 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Chope, E.B., 1889-09-05 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Chope, E.B., 1889-09-18 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Chope, E.B., 1890-05-15 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Chope, E.B., 1890-08-05 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Chopin, C.H., 1891-08-03 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Christiance, R.C., 1886-11-15 (Box 2, Folder 19)
        Boots
      - Christiance, R.C., 1892-05-20 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Church, Irving Porter, 1890-09-20 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Church, Irving Porter, 1890-10-11 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Church, Irving Porter, 1890-10-16 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Claflin, H., 1892-01-19 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Clark, L. Curran, 1892-02-27 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Clark, Tracy Earl, 1892-05-23 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Clark, Tracy Earl, 1894-08-15 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Clarke, Samuel Fessenden, 1886-09-24 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Clinton, C.M., 1888-06-06 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Cochrane, Stacey A., 1887-01-20 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        cousin of Mrs. Comstock
      - Cochrane, Stacey A., 1892-03-09 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Cochrane, Stacey A., 1899-04-29 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Cockerell, Theodore Dru Alison, 1891-12-30 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Cockerell, Theodore Dru Alison, 1892-02-08 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Cockerell, Theodore Dru Alison, 1892-06-15 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Cockerell, Theodore Dru Alison, 1892-07-20 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Cole, Aaron Hodgman, 1889-10-01 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Cole, Aaron Hodgman, 1890-12-01 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Cole, Emma Jane, 1889-06-08 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Colman, Norman Jay, 1887-04-18 (Box 2, Folder 22)
        Journalist
      - Colman, Norman Jay, 1887-05-13 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Colton, George Henry, 1892-05-23 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Comstock, Katherine B., 1900-04-06 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Comstock, Theodore Bryant, 1886-11-20 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Comstock, Theodore Bryant, 1890-08-19 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Comstock, Theodore Bryant, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1881-10-24 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        Naturalist, Michigan Agricultural College
      - Cook, Albert John, 1884 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1885-01-11 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1885-04-23 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1885-05-15 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1885-10-03 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1885-10-08 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1885-11-10 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1885-12-31 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1886-02-04 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1886-04-10 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1886-07-13 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1886-07-19 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1887-07-20 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1887-08-31 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1887-10-15 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1888-06-07 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1888-06-14 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1888-06-21 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1888-09-12 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1888-09-21 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1890-01-17 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1890-12-17 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1891-01-05 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1891-06-11 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1891-06-18 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1891-07-23 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Cook, Albert John, 1892-11-10 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Cook, Albert John, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Cook, Alice Carter, 1893-11-07 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Cook, Henry C.M., 1891-12-31 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Cook, Melville Thurston, 1892-06-20 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Cook, Thomas and Sons, 1891-12-10 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Cooke, Robert J., 1887-09-29 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Coon, Henry C., 1889-12-03 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1887-02-19 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1887-02-24 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1887-03-07 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1887-10-03 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1887-10-13 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1887-10-20 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1887-11-21 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1887-12-13 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1888-02-06 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1888-08-23 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1888-11-22 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1888-12-07 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1888-12-12 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1889-05-21 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1889-08-08 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1889-08-28 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1889-09-08 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1889-09-11 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1889-10-10 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1890-01-10 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1890-02-05 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1890-04-03 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Cope, Edward Drinker, 1891-12-09 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Copeland, Ernest Roscoe, 1891-10-27 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Coquillett, Daniel William, 1887-04-27 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Coquillett, Daniel William, 1887-09-26 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Coquillett, Daniel William, 1889-10-11 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Coquillett, Daniel William, 1890-01-01 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Coquillett, Daniel William, 1890-05-04 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Corbnell University Farmers Institute, 1886-02 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Cordley, Arthur Burton, 1890-12-26 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Cornell Daily Sun, 1886-03-31 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Cornell Daily Sun, 1887-12-14 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Cornell Daily Sun, 1888-11-15 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Cornell Daily Sun, 1889-10-29 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Cornell Daily Sun, 1890-11-15 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Cornell Daily Sun, 1892-04-19 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Cornell Daily Sun, 1892-05-26 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Cornell Daily Sun, 1892-12-20 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Cornell Era, 1886-03-31 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Cornell Era, 1887-12-14 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Cornell Era, 1888-11-15 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Cornell Era, 1889-10-26 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Cornell Era, 1890-11-15 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Cornell Era, 1892-12-20 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Cornell Era, 1894-01-20 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Cornell Magazine, 1888-11-15 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Cornell Magazine, 1894-02-01 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Cornell Union, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Cornell University, 1890-07-24 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Cornell University, 1890-08-01 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Cornell University, 1890-09-01 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Cornell University, 1890-10-01 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Cornell University, 1891-07-24 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Cornell University, 1891-10-08 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Cornell University, 1891-10-23 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Cornell University, 1893-05-02 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Cornell University, 1893-05-23 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Cornell University, 1894-04-10 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Cornell University, 1894-07-07 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Cornell University, 1894-07-12 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Cornell University, 1894-11-21 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Cornell University, 1897-04-05 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Cornell University, 1897-11-01 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Cornell University, 1897-12-01 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Cornell University, 1898-01-01 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Cornell University, 1899-08-01 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Cornell University, 1899-11-01 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Cornell University, 1899-11-22 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Cornell University Alumni Association, 1889-03 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Cornell University Alumni Association, 1896-09-01 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Cornell University Club, 1889-11-21 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Cornell, Alonzo B., Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Corning, Erastus, Jr., 1889-05-17 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Corson, Eugene Rollin, 1893-06-06 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Corson, Eugene Rollin, 1893-09-19 (Box 5, Folder 21)